minecraft101.net 2019-08-22

# Privacy Policy | Minecraft 101

## Short version.

We do not collect any personal information, or use any technology such as cookies to track or identify visitors to the site.

We do, however, use [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) to understand how many people are visiting which pages on the site, and [Google Adsense](https://google.com/privacy/ads/) to pay the bills. These products do use cookies to track users’ behaviour and history, but we at minecraft101.net do not have access to any personally identifying information.

## Longer version.

**Minecraft 101** does not require registration. We don’t have any information that we could use to identify you individually.

Minecraft 101 uses third-party companies to collect and report detailed statistics about site use, but these statistics do not identify individual users, except to the extent that you may have provided this information to those companies.

### Cookies

We may use third party products to display ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. These social media, advertising and analytics partners use cookies (small pieces of data saved on your computer) in order to work properly. Each third-party company has its own privacy policy.

#### Google AdSense

Minecraft 101 uses Google AdSense, a third-party advertising service operated by Google Inc., to serve ads when you visit Yesterland. Google AdSense may use “DoubleClick DART cookie” technology to track information about your visits to Yesterland and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that Google AdSense determines might be of interest to you. Google AdSense does not track your name, address, email address, or telephone number. If you would like more information about this practice, and to know your choices about not having this information used in this way, please refer to [Google’s policies](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

#### Google Analytics

Minecraft 101 uses Google Analytics, a third-party website analysis service operated by Google Inc., to collect and report detailed statistics about visits to Yesterland. When you visit Minecraft 101, Google Analytics servers automatically record and collect Log Data sent by your browser, including your computer’s IP address and the referring HTTP location. Google Analytics’ reporting is private. Google Analytics may place or read cookies. If you would like more information about cookies for Google Analytics, please see [Google’s Privacy statement](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).

### Server logs

As is the usual case on web servers, each web transaction (request for HTML code and images) is recorded in a daily log file. This log file includes information such as your IP address, browser type, and operating system. The log does not include your name, address, email address, or telephone number. The log is used as input to produce reports of website statistics.

### Silktide Cookie Consent

The European Union says we need you consent to having cookies laced on your computer. We’ve used a script provided by [Silktide](https://silktide.com/tools/cookie-consent/) to do this, and they of course set a cookie to remember this consent and not bother you so often.

### Other

Minecraft 101 reserves the right to add or remove third-party affiliate programs and other links, without updating this privacy statement. Minecraft 101 reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time without notice.

## Opting out

It is possible to opt out of the the third party solutions we use.

You can disable all the Doubleclick Cookies by clicking on: [google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en).

It is also possible to control which cookies are accepted by your browser in that program’s preferences/settings.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our site that link to third party sites and services. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our site. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

### Changes to this privacy policy

Minecraft 101 has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will change the date at the bottom of this page.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.

This document was last updated on July 10, 2015
